Perhaps Aria should meet you.
After all, what she truly seeks is hope.
After what I just saw, you could show her that
she's in retreat beyond those mountains, the ice rasps.
You'll have to walk the shaman's path to get there, follow the markers through the ice caves and the waterfalls and make the climb to the shrine.
But be careful.
The path is meant to be an ordeal, the final trial of a young shamans training, and I'll find a ray at the end of it.
No, she goes further up.
Somewhere inside the mountain.
You'll know you've reached the end when you come to a shrine, a great machine covered in blue gleam shamans who complete the path.
Take a piece of it as reward.
If you make it that far, you should, too.
You'll have earned it.
I'm pretty for the shamans path must be around here somewhere.
This must be one of the markers not too told me about.
Looks like each America points to another, giving directions
wrong way.
Go
deeper into the cold.
Creepy.
This isn't the way out.
Some gear, though.
What's this for?
To help guide the way with sound.
If there's more.
Maybe my focus could find them.
Yep.
Focus can pick up the chimes.
Should help me find my way.
Yeah,
Another marker.
Good.
This isn't the way out.
Some gear, though.
Wait.
Yes.
I took a wrong turn.
Yeah,
not this way.
And
we'll see.
Yeah,
Stalkers.
Be careful.
Go
from here.
Yeah.
Better go back after I grab this loot.
No.
Quickly out of this cave.
Okay.
Done with the cave.
What's next on this path?
Wait, Go
across this one
down.
Looks like I need to get up to that.
Rope.
Down is
cheers.
I need to pull the road to move this thing into position.
Okay?
Just
you?
Yeah,
that's it.
Forget what one feels.
No,
I
wasn't exaggerating.
There's definitely something new out here,
but I don't think it's friendly.
What?
Yeah.
No,
no.
With
I got too much already.
Frost claw.
Weakness to fire.
Strong against free's free sack.
Destroying this component triggers a freeze explosion, inflicts a temporary brittle state on the machine and disables the freeze attacks of the claws.
Freeze unit.
Destroying this component disables all freeze based attacks.
Other than Klaus Power cell
E.
Thanks.
Scary machine down
now.
back to finding Maria,
which means we gotta climb.
I should be able to get there.
You
good?
Yeah.
Must be The shrine l took was talking about because I should take some blue gleam sparkles.
You can see why it's worth a lot
now.
Took said Ray went past the shrine into the mountains.
I'd better take those stairs
in Ancient door.
Maybe Ori is inside.
March 10th, 2046.
I just spent 16 hours in here.
Joined to instal upgrades to our fuel efficiency for the central processing unit.
Project Fire Break is going to meet brain power.
Let's just hope I'll have enough of my own.
I need a state with me the whole time.
We got a lot done.
But every time she brushed by, I smelled her hair.
I should just go
go.
Lots of strange equipment.
What was this place?
Okay.
What?
Maybe my focus can help.
Looks like that there was wired something over here.
Okay,
this is Director of Security Blevins.
Resending the emergency supply order.
Try reading at this time, okay?
You weasels don't want me calling my people in Estelle Scene
Director of Security Elevens is writing us like a petty tyrant.
I can't even sneeze without triggering his control issues
Whose nose on the floor must be connected to the door.
Okay, I've been hearing that some of our staff members are having trouble with our state of the art.
Ultra secure and absolutely necessary.
Lam Mentor, Vehicular door access.
So here's the S L O W.
Version.
Again, The thing in the middle is the source note turned it on.
Yeah, I know.
Hard.
Right.
Then you've got to turn the other notes so that the data stream containing your credentials gets back to the source.
Some notes air used to buffer, corrupt or suspect data.
So avoid those Shouldn't be too tough because, you know, they're read like a stop sign.
I'm guessing you were taught this in preschool, but with this crowd, who knows?
Anyway, that's it.
Get the data stream back to the source and the door opens.
It's really not that tough, but if you need me to, I'll hold your hand while you give it a try.
Actually, scratch that.
Do it yourself.
I'm not going to touch your hand.
Something
am I supposed to do with these lights?
Things are changing for flight.
All right.
Yeah.
Another email from my sister.
I haven't got time to think, let alone why?
Photo of the girl.
She said to do much for my conscience.
Jenny looks pretty proud of her pilgrim costume.
I have never missed Thanksgiving before.
Chances for Christmas near Su.
I can't even tell him that all the work I'm doing is to keep him safe.
How long they're going to explain to any fire break this doomed without a guiding intelligence.
Advanced enough not only to think to feel.
Yeah,
fresh air head.
Okay,
let me begin by spelling out disaster for you.
A destructive event causing a level of disturbance.
Unmanageable value.
The application of ordinary resource is what you have given us is distinctly ordinary dummies.
Version.
Give me what I need where you'll be on auto car to lay off city quicker than you can say Code red the list one more time.
3000 memories.
30 military grade flashlights.
No more junk store crap.
10 portable water pumps.
Not five.
Not 8.
10.
50 tubes of fungicide were working underground Sports happened 15 hydraulic jacks, 12 replacement drone propulsion units 50 holographic micro drives in a disaster.
See definition above.
It's absolutely critical to track all ingress and egress is of the facility.
I take our safety seriously, even if you don't.
50 almond scented extra soft David Corrupt
Anita Sandoval.
A personal log.
If Levings reconfigures the pattern on the lamp and tore vehicular door access one more time, I'm going to vomit all over it.
Sure, I don't want some gift shop employee rooting around in the firebreak facility, but these measures aren't about security there about control.
I wonder if Blevins gets in early to watch.
Everybody tried to solve the new pattern perched over his little camera array in his big boy office.
What a bridge troll.
You'd think that a fraction of his fancy drone budget could go toward buying him some classy or body spray.
God helped me and Kenny, if he ever finds out about us
and Nina Sandoval a personal log.
0, 00.6.
What does it mean to quantify an intelligence anyway?
You can't just assign a number on a continuing to a conscious mind and then expected to obey whatever arbitrary limit that number represents.
There's no way around it without the supervision of a mind beyond human capacities.
Firebreak is going to fail.
No 0.6 won't cut it either.
By pushing sentence, you inevitably generate a system that can experience emotion.
Wild, sloppy, unmanageable emotion.
You're capable of abstract thought.
You're capable of fear.
Like best silver.
I won't go through that again.
I categorically refuse.
Hopefully I can get this all across to Kenny.
I like him.
I like his lopsided little smile.
I especially like those circles he makes with his hands when he gets excited about an idea.
If we hadn't been flung together like this, maybe he and I Well, no point in wool gathering, I wonder.
Could an artificial brain experience the singular combination of desire and preemptive regret?